foreign
[Music]
and just like that Autumn is gone the
snow came last week then turned into a
blizzard that left everything buried
under a thick blanket of snow
we usually don't get this much so early
in November and I have a feeling it's
going to be a long winter
[Music]
even though I don't always deal with the
cold well I'm excited for what this
season represents It's Time For Peace
and renewal to go into the quiet with
Grace and a humble heart
the winter fairies are fearsome
creatures but they have much to teach us
I think this time of year challenges me
to learn about my inner self as I cozy
up in my home to wait for the new year
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I've made countless videos on we were
living why I chose it and why it works
for me but I wanted to consider another
side to my reasons to keep living out
here
and that story starts at five years old
even though due to my father's job I was
mostly schooled at home I did have the
opportunity to go for a bit to an
enrichment program on the weekends
spending time with other students and
teachers
while I was there many of my superiors
noticed I was having a hard time
listening and following instructions
my mind would wander and the noisy
environment would constantly distract me
with so many smells sights colors sounds
surrounding me in my classroom I was
overwhelmed
foreign
[Music]
I got tested for a variety of things but
all that was found for certain was that
I love to read and write and create and
though I struggled a bit socially I was
a happy child with a love of learning
and to my mother that was What mattered
I loved chaotic and busy places I wanted
to travel and explore but I needed a
place to go to be myself in quietness I
didn't have to live in a rural area to
find that haven I could create a version
of it most anywhere but once I got the
opportunity to work as a preschool
teacher in this little Valley I had a
feeling I was going to be here long term
and so far it is true I'm ever grateful
and humbled by that opportunity
[Music]
thank you
many people like my lovely sister much
prefer the city environment and couldn't
imagine living anywhere else and to this
day I love to visit her and experience
the immense wonder that is a metropolis
it's exciting and I can enjoy it while
still looking forward to returning to my
life in the countryside
and I think this contrast is the reason
living out here doesn't work for
everyone it is quiet too quiet for many
I know people often joke that that
sounds great but the reality of it can
be hard sometimes even for me
however I knew from a young age that I'd
enjoy living in a place where I could
experience more of that slowness giving
my body a nervous system of safe space
I'm in an environment that aids me but I
can apply these things wherever I live
that is why we were living works for me
as a sensitive person I thrive in an
environment where I can find that simple
space
and don't get me wrong I think you can
create that space Wherever You Are
I treated my former apartment in the
city as my Haven after a long day I had
a closet full of pillows where I would
sit and listen to calming music if I
felt drained
I had a weighted blanket I'd lay on top
of me if I couldn't sleep and it would
help me relax
I had boundaries in regards to
socializing so that I could have time to
rejuvenate
and if you think any of this sounds
strange or abnormal I've heard it before
but I think it's more important to
understand and honor who you are and
find ways to bring peace into your life
if you need it and not worry so much
about being labeled as odd or unusual
I've been able to keep creating videos
start my little Etsy shop and even work
at a couple bookstores because I keep
learning how to listen to what I need
both my lifestyle and priorities and
that has helped me be someone I'm proud
of
you don't need to live in the
countryside if you're a sensitive person
not at all but you do need to accept and
embrace who you are I firmly believe
that every well-adjusted individual has
a hint of strangeness and Whimsy in
their person or if not it's simply
waiting to be discovered
[Music]
thank you
foreign
it has been a lovely week over here and
very quiet I've not yet gotten the snow
tires changed on my car so I'm trying
not to drive too much and it kind of
feels like I'm snowed in so I've been
taking all this time to create some
ornaments and other craft projects for
my family
I'm getting an early start on winter
holiday gifts and I wanted to try to
create some clay ornaments with dried
flowers as well as some paper flowers I
saw some tutorials online I really
wanted to try I hope these give you some
ideas if you're trying to make your own
gifts this year
and I appreciate you being here thank
you so much my Etsy Shop will be closing
in a couple weeks for the month of
December I appreciate your support of my
work and this channel
I hope you have a beautiful week do you
send the winter fairies well wishes they
are working so hard over here to cover
every inch of this Valley with snow
foreign
I always knew that I would be suited to
living in the countryside comes very
naturally to my personality one of the
reasons I started this channel was
because I was aware that rural living
really does not work for everyone and
that's wonderful because that means we
are all different and unique and that's
it's really important I did however want
to share a little bit of the nature and
the beauty of wildlands hopefully
Inspire other people to get involved in
the preservation of these beautiful
areas I think it is so lovely to have a
platform where artists can share their
short films and their creative Endeavors
I think for me I've always described
these videos as my own way of immersing
myself in a fairy tale and I love to
find angles and interesting ways of
portraying the beauty of Nature and home
life these videos are often my way to
celebrate the beauty and life and the
Wonder and Whimsy of the world while
still sharing the natural ups and downs
that all humans deal with I'm so
grateful that I have found other people
that also appreciate that and that more
artistic take on life I will be taking a
little bit of a break from YouTube it's
going to be short but I really had some
more personal things I wanted to figure
out and a little bit more of an idea of
what I want to do in the future I
realized there were some things that I
really need to figure out in regards to
work and my schedule and some personal
things as well so I'm going to be taking
some time this week to think about that
and how that may or may not impact this
channel so I'm sending all of you my
love thank you again sending you kisses
from the snow fairies because they are
working so hard goodbye
foreign
[Music]